[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the reason for the insane behavior of Merlin the wizard from the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "He has suffered a nervous breakdown.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is under a spell.", "He is possessed by a spirit.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He said, You look better than Veronica Lake. She said,  Some men get the world. Others get ex-hookers and a trip to Arizona. Kim Basinger played Lynn Bracken. What actor played Wendell Bud White?", "correct_answer": "Russell Crowe", "incorrect_answers": ["Guy Pearce", "Simon Baker", "Kevin Spacey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2002, which manufacturer launched the first windows-powered cell phone, originally known as codename canary?", "correct_answer": "HTC", "incorrect_answers": ["LG", "Nokia", "Samsung"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the second planet from the Sun called by the Greeks?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Aphrodite", "Phosphorus", "Hesperus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor is known for his comedic roles in the movies Wedding Crashers and Zoolander?", "correct_answer": "Owen Wilson", "incorrect_answers": ["Bradley Cooper", "Christopher Walken", "Vince Vaughn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The wedding cake originated in ancient Rome where it was thrown at the bride or broken over her head as a sign of fertility.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What shouldnt perfumes and fragrances be exposed to in order to preserve their properties longer?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Light", "Heat", "Oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the largest in terms of area?", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia", "Florida", "Finland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Smokey and the Bandit, Sally Fields character complained that she didnt have a CB handle or nickname. What nickname did the Bandit give her?", "correct_answer": "Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabbit", "Crazy Lady", "Toad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Romanian dish, widely known around the world under the Italian name of polenta, is traditionally prepared of maize, cooked in an iron pot.", "correct_answer": "M\u0103m\u0103lig\u0103", "incorrect_answers": ["Vesalica", "Hornazo", "Pilaf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which insects does the science called Coleopterology study?", "correct_answer": "Beetles", "incorrect_answers": ["Mosquitoes", "Mantises", "Parasitic insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the word used for someone that is afraid of chickens?", "correct_answer": "Alektorphobic", "incorrect_answers": ["Xenophobic", "Chickopobic", "Avianphobic"]}]